Eldor Karimov

python backend engineer

19.02.2000 +998973950072 Tashkent, Uzbekistan karimoveldor19021@gmail.com

About Me

I am a Python Backend Engineer. I have been involved in several projects. I want to participate in bigger projects and gain experience. I will be happy to join an enthusiastic and friendly team.

LinkedIn: @eldor-karimov-057323223/
 Telegram: @hacktivist_07

· Github: @eldorkarimov

Work Experience

Backend Developer at Diamond Solutions

Oct 2022 — Dec 2022

diamondsolutions.uz/ Part-time

-used MVT architecture to build Library management system

- used Python, Django, PostgreSql and many more
- Website development in Django, Django Rest
- create complex UI with JavaScript, VueJS, Bootstrap, CSS, HTML

Backend Developer at IT Park Urgut

Feb 2022 — Jul 2022

it-park.uz Part-time

- taught to code in python backend
- do code review once in a week

Education

Tashkent University of Information Technologies SB

2019 - 2023

Information Security - Bachelor's degree

GPA: 4.5/5

Languages

• Uzbek - Native

• Russian - B1 - Intermediate

• English - B1 - Intermediate

Skills

Python Git Django Algorithms C++ Django REST Framework (DRF)

PostgreSQL Telegram Bot API Aiogram GitHub Back End (Software Engineering)

Licenses and Certificates

Full Stack Developer Track

One Million Uzbek Coders